<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Joshua Carr - User Experience | Software Development | Human Factors</title>
    <link>https://jcarr.xyz/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Joshua Carr - User Experience | Software Development | Human Factors</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 21 Aug 2021 11:20:22 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jcarr.xyz/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Portfolio (about this site)</title>
      <link>https://jcarr.xyz/projects/portfolio_site/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Aug 2021 11:20:22 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jcarr.xyz/projects/portfolio_site/</guid>
      <description>I wanted to create a simple and easy-to-maintain site to host my personal portfolio. I decided to use the static-site generator Hugo for this project. Hugo allows me to use Markdown (which I use for everything already) to write posts for the site, and publishing is as simple as pushing commits to a remote git repository which triggers automated CI/CD into Netlify&amp;rsquo;s CDN. I used the Hermit Hugo theme as a base and made some minor modifications.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://jcarr.xyz/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Oct 2020 16:19:50 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jcarr.xyz/about/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m a researcher and data analyst specializing in human-factors in computing. I have a multi-disciplinary background which includes experience in user experience research, molecular neurobiology, cognitive science, software development, quantitative and qualitative data analysis, machine learning, and healthcare. I earned the degrees of Bachelor of Science in Psychology from Trent University in 2015 and Master of Applied Science in Human-Computer Interaction from Carleton University in 2020.
This site is intended as a showcase and repository of my work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brain-Computer Interface Expert Interview Study</title>
      <link>https://jcarr.xyz/projects/bci_interview_study/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jcarr.xyz/projects/bci_interview_study/</guid>
      <description>by Joshua Carr This post describes a study that I completed as a part of my HCI Master&amp;rsquo;s thesis at Carleton University. This was a qualitative interview study which was aimed at understanding factors related to acceptance and adoption of brain-computer interface (BCI) devices by the public. This project was originally published as Chapter 4 of my Master&amp;rsquo;s thesis, available here.
Organization  Carleton University - Human-Oriented Technology Software Research Lab (HotSoft) Supervised by Dr.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
